Dimitrie Străoanu Web Designer | Developer



https://dimitriestraoanu.com



An enthusiastic, passionate and creative web designer/developer proficient with JavaScript, HTML and CSS. Quik learner, detail-oriented and a team player with excellent communication skills. I can create beautiful, responsive and user-friendly websites using only core web technologies or by using a CMS(Wordpress) for a more feature rich experience.

Work experience:

2019

Web Designer/Developer

Self-employed Department: IT

2017 - 2019 | 2 ani

Designer

TRUSTEAM - București Department: Graphics | Industry: Advertisement

2008 - 2016 | 9 ani

Designer

Laris Production - Focşani Department: Graphics | Industry: Advertisement

2003 - 2008 | 5 ani

Designer

Caspro - Focșani

Department: Graphics | Industry: Advertisement

Education:

2019

Web Development

Scoala Informala de IT, București

1993 - 1997

High School | IT

Colegiul National Unirea, Focșani

Certificates:

2019

Programmer Certificate

released by National Authority for Qualifications

Technical skills:

JavaScript ES6 HTML5 CSS3 **Bootstrap** Wordpress

Git/GitHub **NPM** Webpack Babel

VS Code **Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Animate Figma** CorelDraw **SolidWorks**

Personal skills:

Passionate Creative **Detail oriented Quick learner** Organized

Languages:

English